《侏罗纪世界》
孩子们 出发了
Boys, let's do this!
格雷
Gray?
亲爱的 你在做什么
Honey, what are you doing?
这是什么 我们该走了
What is this here? Let's go.
快点 亲爱的 你的航班还有两小时就要起飞了
Come on, honey. Your flight's in two hours.
从这到戴恩机场要36分钟 堵车的话要一小时
Dane County Airport is 36 minutes away, 60 with traffic.
把你的屁股挪进车里要多久
How many minutes to get your little butt in the van?
要多久呢
How many of those?
- 给你床下的小怪兽喂食了吗 - 是的
- Feed the monster under your bed? - Yes.
每天给我打电话
Call me every day...
给我发照片 这样我就不会忘记你这张帅脸
and text me pics so I don't forget what you look like.
我只去一个星期
I'm only gonna be gone a week.
扎克
Zach.
你们又不是生离死别 拜托
You're not going off to war here. Please.
快点
Come on.
- 回见 - 我爱你
- I will see you later. - I love you.
- 再见 好吗 - 再见
- Bye, okay? - Bye.
你上车了吗
Are you in, buddy?
我知道分离很心痛 亲爱的
I know it hurts, sweetheart.
你还好吗
Are you gonna be okay?
没什么问题吧
Everything right on there?
我真羡慕
I'm so jealous.
你们会玩得非常开心的 我爱你
You're gonna have so much fun. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
好的 很好
Okay, great.
好了 我把这些交给你哥哥 可以吗
All right, let's give these to your brother, okay?
你拿好这些 你能拿着这些吗
You hold these, please. Can you hold these?
- 亲爱的 我要你保管好这些 - 好的
- Honey, I need you to take care of these. - Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
- 好了 - 好好听你妈妈说话
- Alright. - Listen to your mother.
照顾好你弟弟 记得接电话
Take care of your brother. Answer your phone.
我很认真的 就是那个绿色的按键
I'm serious. It's the green button.
当你看到我的名字 就按下它 明白吗
When you see my name, push it, okay?
还有记住 有东西追你的话 跑
And remember... something chases you, run.
走吧
Come on.
- 好吧 - 你真幽默 好了 我们出发吧
- All right. - You're funny. Okay, let's go. Come on.
- 再见 孩子们 - 再见
- Bye, guys. - Bye.
- 我已经开始想你们了 - 好吧
- I miss you already. - Yeah.
真像是我们家的最后一次早餐
So much for our last family breakfast.
你为什么要说这种话
Why do you have to say things like that?
你给你妹妹打电话了吗
Did you call your sister?
转到语音信箱了
Straight to voice-mail.
没事的
It'll be fine.
她一天要接待两万位游客呢
She handles 20,000 people a day, right?
多两个不是问题
She can handle two more.
(哥斯达黎加 胡安 圣塔马利亚机场)
这个岛有多大
How big is the island?
很大
Big.
有多重
But how many pounds?
你这个问题问得有问题
That doesn't make sense.
他们最初开放的时候 只有八个种类
When they first opened, they had 8 species.
现在他们有14种食草恐龙和6种食肉恐龙
Now they have 14 herbivores and 6 carnivores.
一周要吃掉50吨的食物
That's 50 tons of food a week.
欢迎来到努布拉岛 侏罗纪世界之家
Welcome to Isla Nublar, home of Jurassic World.
希望您能在此有一段安全而愉快的探险之旅
We hope you have a safe and enjoyable stay with us.
(扎克和格雷 米切尔)
克莱尔阿姨在哪儿
Where's Aunt Claire?
坐在列车前排的游客
Those of you in the front of
可以看到我们的大门
the train should be able to see our main gates.
(侏罗纪世界)
请遵守所有园区规则
Please obey all park rules.
请着装得体 包括鞋子和衬衫
Proper attire, including shoes and shirts,
也必须时刻穿戴整齐
must be worn at all times.
你们的阿姨安排一点钟见你们 他能慢点走吗
Your aunt arranged to meet you at 1:00. Can he slow down?
不能
Nope.
快来
Come on!
你阿姨给你们开通了贵宾通道
Your aunt's got you VIP access...
你们可以不用排队一路畅玩
so you can get in all the rides without waiting in line.
快去玩吧
Let's go.
老弟 她说我们要等一会儿
Dude, she said we had to wait.
我不想再等了
I don't wanna wait anymore.
哈尔·奥斯特利是副总裁 吉姆·德鲁克是谢顶
Hal Osterley, vice president. Jim Drucker, bad hair.
埃里卡·布兰德 时运不济
Erica Brand, deserves better.
哈尔 吉姆 埃里卡 哈尔 吉姆 埃里卡
Hal, Jim, Erica. Hal, Jim, Erica.
我是克莱尔
And I am Claire.
迟到了三分钟
Three minutes late.
欢迎来到侏罗纪世界
Welcome to Jurassic World.
年复一年 收入保持增长
While year over year, revenue continues to climb...
同时运营成本也比过去高出许多
operating costs are higher than ever.
虽然我们的投资者一直很有耐心 但是坦白说
Our shareholders have been patient but let's be honest...
没有人再对恐龙感到新奇
no one is impressed by a dinosaur anymore.
20年前 复活灭绝物种就像魔法
20 years ago, de-extinction was right up there with magic.
而现在 孩子们看见一只
These days, kids look at a
剑龙就像在城市动物园看见大象一样
Stegosaurus like an elephant from the city zoo.
这并不意味资产发展已经落后了
That doesn't mean asset development is falling behind.
我们的基因发掘家每年都会探索出新的物种
Our DNA excavators discover new species every year.
但是消费者想看体型更大 叫声更响 牙齿更多的动物
But consumers want them bigger, louder, more teeth.
好消息是
The good news?
我们在基因融合领域的
Our advances in gene
改进已经开辟了一个新的前沿
splicing have opened up a whole new frontier.
相比挖骨头的那个世纪 过去十年我们
We've learned more from genetics in the past decade...
从遗传学中学到了更多
than a century of digging up bones.
所以
So...
当你想吸引赞助商
when you say you want to sponsor an attraction...
你脑中想起的是什么
what do you have in mind?
我们想要兴奋刺激的感觉
We want to be thrilled.
谁不是呢
Don't we all?
暴虐霸王龙 我们的第一个转基因混血恐龙
The Indominus Rex. Our first genetically modified hybrid.
你们怎么让两种不同的恐龙内啥 你懂的
How did you get two different kinds of dinosaurs to, you know...
哦 暴虐霸王龙不是繁殖出来的 她是设计出来的
Oh, Indominus wasn't bred. She was designed.
成熟后她将有50英尺长
She will be 50 feet long when fully grown.
比霸王龙体型还要大
Bigger than the T. Rex.
每次我们推出一个新的资产的时候 入场率都会飙升
Every time we've unveiled a new asset, attendance has spiked.
全球新闻头条
Global news coverage...
各界名流参观
celebrity visitors.
世界瞩目
Eyes of the world.
她什么时候能准备好
When will she be ready?
她已经准备好了
She already is.
快来
Come on!
别激动
Relax.
快啊
Come on.
老弟 冷静点
Dude, chill.
(哈蒙德创意实验室)
欢迎来到创新中心
Welcome to the Innovation Center,
在这里科技见证史前时代
where technology meets prehistory.
可以与顶端食肉动物角牙搏斗
can go horn-to-tooth with the apex predators.
希腊语的字面意思是三角面
Literally meaning "Three-horned face" In Greek...
三角恐龙只有T霸王龙的一半高
Triceratops is half as tall as T. Rex
它的威力有如一百万亿吨的炸药
as one-hundred trillion tons of TNT.
转头看向背后
turn its head back to look over its shoulder...
来更好地甩动它那危险的尾巴瞄准敌人
to better aim the swing of its dangerous tail.
氧氨嘧啶 鸟嘌呤 腺嘌呤和胸腺嘧啶（核酸主要成分）
Cytosine, guanine, adenine and thymine.
一切生物都有的四种物质
The same four things in everything that ever lived.
嘿 别到处乱跑 好吗
Hey, don't wander off, all right?
妈妈不会为我照顾孩子付钱的
Mom's not paying me for babysitting.
格雷 是你吗
Gray, is that you?
克莱尔阿姨
Aunt Claire!
好的 是的 不 我要挂电话了 我的侄子们来了
Okay, yeah. No, I'm gonna have to go. My nephews are here.
嗨
Hi.
哦 我的天哪 你真可爱
Oh, my gosh, you're so sweet.
喔 扎克
Whoa, Zach.
我上次见你的时候 你只有
Last time I saw you, you were like...
多少年前来着
That must've been what?
- 三四年前 - 七年前
- Three, four years ago? - Seven.
七年前 但是 已经很接近了
Seven years, but, you know, close.
我看到你们已经拿到腕带了
I see you already got your wristbands.
这是用来买食物的
And this is for food.
这是扎拉 她会照顾好你们的
And Zara here is going to take great care of you...
直到我今晚忙完工作 好吗
until I'm done working tonight, okay?
你不和我们一起去吗
You're not coming with us?
我真希望我可以 但是
I really wish that I could, but...
明天我可以带你们去主控室
tomorrow I can take you into the control room...
让你们看看幕后的一切
show you behind the scenes and all of that.
那一定很酷 不是吗
That's gonna be cool, right?
好的 我今晚六点来找你们
Okay, so I will see you tonight at... 6:00.
不 不 不 别忘了你还有个
No, no, no. Don't forget you have the...
没错 当然 我今晚八点见你们
Right, of course. I will see you tonight at 8:00.
你们几点睡觉
What time do you go to sleep?
还是你们睡觉时间不同
Or do you go to sleep at different times?
好了 玩得开心
Okay, so, have fun...
照顾好他们 好吗
and take very good care of them, okay?
是的 不 我在
Yeah. No, I'm here.
这是两只幼年三角龙 他们又朝它过去了
It's those two juvenile Triceratops. They're going at it again.
我是麻醉它们 还是你来对付它们
Should I tranq them, or are you coming over to take care of this?
- 麻醉它们吧 - 他们跑了
- Go ahead and tranq them. - They're running.
- 今日游园人数是多少 - 22216人
- What's the live count? - 22,216.
- 有什么事故发生吗 - 是的
- Any incidents? - Yes.
有六个孩子走失
Six kids in the Lost and Found...
28名游客中暑
28 down with heatstroke...
你从哪儿买来的那东西
Where did you get that?
哦 这个 我在易趣上买的 它真的很神奇
Oh, this? I got it on eBay. Yeah, it's pretty amazing.
我花150美元买的 不过全新的要300美元
I got it for $150 but the mint condition one goes for $300...
你不觉得它很没品位吗
Didn't occur to you maybe that's in poor taste?
这T恤 不 不会
The shirt? Yeah, no, it did.
我知道有人伤亡 那件事可怕
I understand people died. It was terrible...
但第一个公园是合法的
but that first park was legit.
我超级尊敬它
I have a lot of respect for it.
他们根本不需要这些遗传混血恐龙
They didn't need these genetic hybrids.
他们只需要恐龙 真正的恐龙
They just needed dinosaurs, real dinosaurs.
好吧 拜托别再穿它了
Okay, please don't wear it again.
好的 我不会了
Yeah, I wasn't gonna.
- 你谈成了吗 - 应该没问题
- Did you close the deal? - Looks like it.
威瑞森无线公司出品的暴虐霸王龙
Verizon Wireless presents the Indominus Rex.
真是太可怕了
That is so terrible.
干嘛不更过分点
Why not just go the distance,
直接让这些公司给恐龙命名算了
and just let these corporations name the dinosaurs?
反正他们已经命名了所有棒球场
They've got all the ballparks.
- 何必止步于此呢 - 为什么西部平原关闭了
- Why stop there? - Why are the West Plains closed?
又有一头肿头龙在区域外游荡
Another Pachy roaming outside his zone.
但他已经被麻醉了 准备送回去
But he's fully sedated and ready for relocation.
不如叫百事恐龙或者托斯蒂多滋恐龙（玉米片品牌）
Pepsi-saurus or Tostito-don.
安保说隐形围栏是不会出问题的
Security said the invisible fences were a
这是这个月第二次发生这种事了
no-fail. That is the second time this month.
肿头龙打架的时候把他们的植入物弄短路了
The Pachys short out their implants when they butt heads.
还要多久能把它弄走
How much longer until they get it out of there?
他刚被注射5毫克的镇静剂
He just got five milligrams of carfentanil.
好吧 他已经被麻醉了 我们为什么不能对他略表同情呢
Yes, he's very stoned. So why don't we show a little sympathy?
我是说 你知道他们是有血有肉的动物 对吗
I mean you do understand these are actual animals, right?
把你的工作区清理下
Clean up your workspace.
乱死了
It's chaotic.
我喜欢把它看作是一个生态系统
I like to think of it as a living system.
只要有足够的稳定性
Just enough stability...
就能防止它陷入混乱
to keep it from collapsing into anarchy.
直升飞机已入境 侏罗纪一号 五分钟后抵达
Inbound chopper, Jurassic 1. ETA, 5 minutes.
克莱尔
Claire.
马斯拉尼先生 是你在驾驶啊
Mr. Masrani. You are flying.
我拿到执照了
I got my license.
- 两天后 - 好吧 还差两天
- Two more. - Well, two more days.
- 好的 - 那么
- Okay. - So...
- 我的公园怎么样 - 很好
- how's my park doing? - Great.
去年我们盈利又提升了2.5个百分点
We're up two and a half percent over last year.
比最初预期的低了点
A bit lower than our initial prediction.
不 不 不 我问的是它怎么样
No, no, no, how's it doing?
游客们开心吗 动物们享受生活吗
Are the guests having fun? Are the animals enjoying life?
游客满意度保持在90出头
Well, guest satisfaction is steady in the low 90s.
我们没有办法来衡量动物的情感体验
We don't have a way to measure the animals' emotional experience.
当然有了 你能从它们的眼里看出来
Sure you do. You can see in their eyes.
对吗
Right?
当然了
Of course.
好了 现在去看看我的新恐龙
Okay. Now show me my new dinosaur.
没事
Got it.
我控制住了
控制住了
Got it.
我 我的天
Oh, my!
你看上去很紧张 克莱尔
You look tense, Claire.
也许你应该把注意力集中在驾驶上
Maybe you should just focus on the controls.
幸福生活的关键是
The key to a happy life is
要接受你永远无法真正掌控一切的现实
to accept you are never actually in control.
有鸟
Bird!
你应该去海边放松一天
You should spend a day at the beach.
晒晒太阳
Get some sun.
对了
Right, so...
市场部认为我们可以抵消部分成本
Marketing thought we could offset some of the costs by...
不要提成本
Enough about cost.
约翰·哈蒙德把他的遗愿托付给我
John Hammond entrusted me with his dying wish...
可从没提过什么利润
and not once did he mention profits.
"不惜成本" 他过去总说
Spare no expense, He used to say.
我很欣赏那样 但是
I appreciate that, but the
事实上 运营一个主题公园需要
reality of operating a theme park requires...
别忘了我们建造这里的初衷 克莱尔
Don't forget why we built this place, Claire.
侏罗纪世界的存在是
Jurassic World exists to
为了提醒我们 我们有多渺小 多么年轻
remind us how very small we are. How new.
这种觉悟是无法用金钱估量的
You can't put a price on that.
今朝能飞今朝飞
Now, please, we're flying.
深呼吸享受吧
Breathe.
他还好吗
Is he okay?
- 你还好吗 - 他只是有点夸张
- Are you okay? - He's just being dramatic.
这里还在建造中吗
Are you still building?
我们打算在五月开放
We planned to open in May...
但是资产控制部坚持要我们把墙再建高点
but Asset Containment insisted we build the walls up higher.
它的体型比预期的要大
It's bigger than expected.
这是个好兆头
It's a good sign.
我们前段时间出了点小问题
We hit a few speed bumps early on.
它开始预见食物出现的方向
It began to anticipate where the food would come from.
有一位工作人员差点失去他的胳膊
One of the handlers nearly lost an arm.
其他人威胁说
The others threatened to
如果我不能保证他们的安全就辞职
quit if I couldn't guarantee their safety.
这么说她很聪明喽
She's intelligent then?
对一个恐龙来说是那样
For a dinosaur.
那是什么
And that?
它曾试图弄碎玻璃
It tried to break the glass.
我喜欢她的精神
I like her spirit.
它是白色的 你从没告诉我它是白色的
It's white. You never told me it was white.
你觉得它会吓到孩子们吗
Think it will scare the kids?
孩子们
The kids?
这会让家长们做噩梦的
This will give the parents nightmares.
这是好事吗
Is that good?
这简直好极了
It's fantastic.
她能看到我吗
Can she see us?
他们说它可以感受到热辐射 像蛇一样
They say it can sense thermal radiation. Like snakes.
我以为有两头
I thought there were two of them.
以防它无法成活 它曾有个妹妹
There was a sibling in case this one didn't survive infancy.
妹妹在哪儿
Where's the sibling?
她吃掉了
She ate it.
这围场够安全吗
So, the paddock is quite safe, then?
我们请来了世界上最好的结构工程师
We have the best structural engineers in the world.
是的 哈蒙德也有过
Yeah, so did Hammond.
这里有个美国海军军人
There's an American Navy man here.
是我公司正在进行的一个研究项目的成员
Part of a research program one of my companies is running.
欧文·格雷迪
Owen Grady.
我知道他是谁
I know who he is.
他的动物经常试图逃跑
His animals often try to escape.
它们很聪明 所以他必须更聪明
They are smart. He has to be smarter.
他只认为他更聪明
He only thinks he's smarter.
我想让你带他过来
I want you to bring him in.
让他检查下围场的安全度
Let him inspect the paddock.
毕竟旁观者清
Maybe he sees something we can't.
停
Hold!
嘿
Hey!
好的
Okay!
看着我
Eyes on me.
布鲁
Blue?
Blue!
注意点
Watch it.
查理 嘿
Charlie. Hey!
别给我来这套
Don't give me that shit!
德尔塔
Delta!
集中注意力
Lock it up!
很好
Good!
这边走
And we're moving!
停
Hold!
很好 非常好
That's good. That is damn good.
很好
Very good!
查理 这是你的
See, Charlie, that's what you get!
艾蔻 接着
Echo, there you go!
德尔塔
Delta!
布鲁
Blue?
这个是给你的
This one's for you.
停
Hold!
抬头
Eyes up!
走
Go.
你终于成功了
You finally did it, man.
欧文
Owen.
我开始以为我请错了人呢
I was starting to think I hired the wrong guys...
但是 她们完全在你的掌控之中了
but, damn, you got them eating out of your palm.
你今天来得巧 不是每次结局都这么理想的
You came on a good day. It's not usually a happy ending.
这就是你不把这件事写进报告里的原因吗
Is that why you're not sending in your reports?
我们一直很忙
We've been busy.
领薪水的时候倒是跑得快
Not too busy to cash your paychecks.
你有何贵干 伙计
What do you need, buddy?
实地测试
A field test.
嘿 我刚刚看到他们可以对命令做出回应
Hey. I've just seen they can respond to commands.
我们需要把这项研究利用起来
We need to take the research and get it on its feet.
她们是野兽 霍斯金
These are wild animals, Hoskins.
相信我 你不会希望她们参与实战的
Trust me, you don't want them in the field.
我刚刚看到了情感联系 真正的联系
I just saw a bond. A real bond.
人和野兽之间的联系
Between man and beast.
- 你挡我道了 - 想想看 我们都是一样的
- You're in my way. - Come on. We're the same.
我们都是战争的走狗
We're dogs of war.
我们都知道军队需要减少伤亡
We know that the military needs to reduce casualties.
一些人认为机器人才是未来
Some people think that robots are the future.
听着 大自然在七千五百万年前
Look, nature gave us the most
就给了我们最有效的杀戮机器
effective killing machines 75 million years ago.
而现在我们知道他们可以听从指令
And now we know they can take orders.
我们刚取得进步他就说这个
We finally make progress and that's the first thing he says?
当做武器
Make a weapon?
妈的
Shit.
想想看 伙计们
Come on, gents.
这是成年人的世界
It's grown-up time.
无人机不能搜索隧道和洞穴 还容易被攻击
Drones can't search tunnels and caves. And they're hackable.
一旦真正的战争爆发
The minute a real war breaks out,
所有的高科技都会失效
all that fancy tech is gonna go dark.
高科技可不会在忘了喂它之后吃了他们
But that tech's not gonna eat them if they forget to feed it.
看看这些生物
Look at these creatures.
百万年来 他们的细胞里保留着
They've got millions of years of instinct in
那种我们可以改写的本能
their cells, instinct that we can program.
她们的忠诚是无法被收买的
Their loyalty cannot be bought.
这些家伙将会径直
These guys are gonna run
跑到敌人面前吃了他们
straight into the enemy's teeth and eat them...
骨头都不吐
belt buckle and all.
要是她们想自己做主怎么办
What if they decide they wanna be in control?
那我们就提醒她们自己是谁 消灭那些野兽
Then we remind them who is. We terminate the rogues.
只保留忠诚的血脉
Promote only loyal bloodlines.
什么 笑什么
What? What's so funny?
你来这除了只想了解你想知道的事
You come here and you don't learn anything about these animal,
有关这些动物你却一点都不了解
except what you want to know.
你创造了她们就觉得自己拥有了她们
You made them and now you think you own them.
我们确实拥有她们
We do own them.
已经灭绝的动物没有讨价还价的余地
Extinct animals have no rights.
他们不再是灭绝的动物了 霍斯金
They're not extinct anymore, Hoskins.
没错 我们现在坐拥的是金矿
Exactly. We're sitting on a goldmine.
而马斯拉尼却把这里弄成了一个宠物乐园
And Masrani is using it to stock a petting zoo.
他只是想让人们学会谦卑
He just wants to teach people some humility.
他不是为了制造武器
He doesn't make weapons.
你觉得世界富豪排行第八的人
You think that the 8th richest man in the world...
只对石油 通信和家庭主题公园感兴趣吗
is only into oil, telecom and family fun parks?
他的产业太多元化了 他甚至不清楚自己拥有什么
He's so diversified, he doesn't even know what he owns.
你觉得国际基因科技公司在这个领域研究多久了
How long has INGEN been practicing this pitch?
自从我们把你从海军挖过来之后
Since the day we hired you out of the Navy.
你知道结果会是什么样子
You knew the end game.
这种动物在地面上可以代替成千上万个机器人
These animals can replace thousands of boots on the ground.
这将会拯救多少生命
How many lives would that save?
战争也是自然的一部分
War is part of nature.
看看周围 欧文 生活在这片丛林里的生物
Look around, Owen. Every living thing in this jungle...
都在互相残杀
is trying to murder the other.
这是大自然母亲检测她产物的方式
Mother Nature's way of testing her creations.
调整食物链
Refining the pecking order.
战争就是抗争 抗争孕育伟大
War is a struggle. Struggle breeds greatness.
没有这一切
Without that...
我们就会在这种地方庸碌一辈子 一杯的苏打水卖七块钱
we end up with places like this, charge seven bucks a soda.
你自己说的话你仔细听了吗
Do you hear yourself when you talk?
这是必然的 有没有你们都一样
This is gonna happen. With or without you boys.
进化永远是赢家 伙计
Progress always wins, man.
或许这种进化应该输一回了
Maybe progress should lose for once.
猪跑了
Pig loose!
欧文 不要
Owen, no!
别 别开火
No, hold your fire!
别开火 不要开火
Hold your fire. Do not fire.
用十二安培的电流击中她们 她们就再也不会信任我了
Put 12 amps in these animals, they're never gonna trust me again.
布鲁 退下
Blue, stand down.
退下
Stand down.
嘿 嘿 我刚刚说了什么
Hey! Hey! What did I just say?
德尔塔 我看到你了 退后
Delta, I see you. Back up!
好了
Okay.
好的
Good.
很好
查理
Charlie?
待那别动
Stay right there.
很好
Good.
关上门
Close the gate.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
相信我
Just trust me.
快关门
Close the gate!
是啊
Yeah.
你是新来的 对吧
You're the new guy, right?
是的
Yeah.
你想过为什么这里会有个职位空缺吗
You ever wonder why there was a job opening?
永远别背对笼子
Don't ever turn your back to the cage.
把我举起来 我看不到
Lift me up. I can't see!
我又不是老爸 你也不是五岁小孩
I'm not Dad. And you're not five.
我还能骑三角龙 我才四十七点五英尺高
I can still ride the Triceratops. I'm 47-and-a-half inches.
这个地方是给小孩子准备的
This place is for little kids.
是呀 我知道
Yeah, I know.
- 想去转恐龙蛋吗 - 不想
- Wanna go on the spinning dinosaur eggs? - Nope.
盖好你的呆子腰包
Cover up your dork pouch.
因为这是我的婚礼
It's my wedding.
不行 阿莱克不会举办单身汉派对
No, Alec's not having a bachelor party.
因为他的朋友都是禽兽
Because all his friends are animals.
趁机快溜
Scatter.
- 什么 - 走 快跑 快 快
- What? - Go. Run. Go! Go, go!
霸王龙的下一次喂食表演将在十分钟后开始
The next T. Rex feeding will begin in 10 minutes.
- 霸王龙哎 快点 老哥 - 好吧
- T. Rex! Come on, man! - Okay.
快点
Let's go!
家长请注意 这个
Parents be aware, this
表演可能会对儿童造成不良影响
show may be disturbing for smaller children.
嗨 妈妈
Hey, Mom.
你应该在落地之后给我回电话的
You were supposed to call me when you landed.
玩得开心吗
Are you having fun?
还行吧 我觉得
Yeah, I guess.
克莱尔阿姨给了我们贵宾通行证 这样我们就不用排队了
Aunt Claire gave us passes so we don't have to wait in line.
等等 她没和你们在一起吗
Wait, she's not with you?
嗨 凯伦
Hey, Karen!
嗨 克莱尔 一切还好吗
Hi, Claire. How's it going?
是啊 都挺好的 孩子们玩得很开心
Yeah, everything's great. The boys are having fun.
大家 大家都挺好的
Everyone's... Yeah, everyone's good.
真的吗 因为我刚刚和扎克通过电话
Really? Because I just hung up with Zach and
他说你都没和他们在一起
he said that you weren't even with them.
好吧 听我说 我今天真的很忙
Yeah, look. Today turned out to be a really bad day for me.
有人照顾他们 他们和我的助理在一起
They're in great hands. They're with my assistant.
她是英国人 所以 你知道 保姆就是英国人发明的
She's British, so, like, they invented nannies.
等等 你在哭吗
Wait, are you crying?
这本该是一个家庭团聚周末的 克莱尔
This was supposed to be a family weekend, Claire.
你好久没有见过他们了
You haven't seen the boys in forever.
我知道他们在一块的时候扎克会怎么待格雷
And I know how Zach will treat Gray if they're by themselves.
他会变得很刻薄
And he can just be so mean.
噢 对不起
Okay, I'm sorry.
明天 我会花一整天的时间陪着他们
Tomorrow, I'm gonna spend the entire day with them.
我会请一天假
I'm going to take off work
我会和他们寸步不离的 我保证
and I will not leave their side. I promise.
说得好不如做得好
Well, a promise tomorrow is worth a lot less than trying today.
你这是在引用妈妈的话吗
You're using Mom's lines now?
噢 天啊 我竟然引用了妈妈的话
Oh, my God. I am using Mom's lines.
抱歉 但是你知道确实是这个道理
I'm sorry, but you know I have to tell you they work.
当你有孩子之后就明白了
You'll see when you have kids.
是啊 如果有那一天的话
Yeah, "If."
会有的 有孩子是件好事
When. It's worth it.
拜 妈妈
Bye, Mom.
拜
Bye.
他们又想干什么
What do they want now?
格雷迪先生
Mr. Grady?
我想请你去看点东西
I need you to come take a look at something.
你为什么叫我格雷迪先生
Why are you calling me Mr. Grady?
欧文
Owen.
- 如果你不是很忙的话 - 我忙得很
- If you're not too busy. - I'm pretty busy.
我们遇到了一个问题
We have an attraction.
上一次见你 你可不是这么说的
That's not what you said the last time I saw you.
我指的是恐龙 格雷迪先生
I'm talking about the dinosaurs, Mr. Grady.
叫我欧文
Owen.
我们创造了一个新的物种
A new species we've... made.
你就这么创造了一种新的恐龙
You just went and made a new dinosaur?
没错 我们就是干这行的
Yeah, it's kind of what we do here.
展览将会在三周后对外开放
The exhibit opens to the public in three weeks.
马斯拉尼先生想请你探讨一下
Mr. Masrani wanted me to consult with you.
你是想在这探讨还是 在我的小屋里
You wanna consult here or... in my bungalow?
这一点也不好笑
That's not funny.
有点好笑
A little funny.
我们想请你评估一下围场的牢固程度
We'd like you to evaluate the paddock for vulnerabilities.
为什么找我
Why me?
我想马斯拉尼先生觉得
I guess Mr. Masrani thinks,
既然你能控制迅猛龙
since you're able to control the Raptors...
你脑子里就知道控制
It's all about control with you.
我并不控制迅猛龙 我们之间是有感情的
I don't control the Raptors. It's a relationship.
这基于相互尊重
It's based on mutual respect.
这就是为什么你和我没有第二次约会
That's why you and I never had a second date.
什么 是我从来没想过再和你约会
Excuse me? I never wanted a second date.
谁会把约会行程打印出来
Who prints out an itinerary for a night out?
我是个非常有条理的人
I'm an organized person.
什么样饭局连龙舌兰都不能喝
What kind of a diet doesn't allow tequila?
其实 所有的饭局都不能喝
All of them, actually.
另外 什么样的男人会穿着沙滩裤去约会
And what kind of a man shows up to a date in board shorts?
这是中美洲 热得很
It's Central America. It's hot.
好吧 好吧 我们能把重点放在资产上吗
Okay, okay. Can we just focus on the asset, please?
资产
The asset?
听着 我懂 这里你说的算
Look, I get it. You're in charge out here.
你有很多艰难的决定要做
You gotta make a lot of tough decisions.
或许把这些动物当做表格上的
It's probably easier to pretend
数字会让人好受些
these animals are just numbers on a spreadsheet.
但她们不是 她们是有生命的
But they're not. They're alive.
我当然知道她们是有生命的
I'm fully aware they're alive.
没错 你在试管里创造了她们
You might have made them in a test tube,
但是她们不知道这一点
but they don't know that.
她们在想 我饿了
They're thinking, "I gotta eat."
我要捕猎 我要啪啪啪
I gotta hunt. I gotta...
你至少能理解我说的其中一件事 对吧
You can relate to at least one of those things. Right?
我在车里等你
I'll be in the car.
你得换件衣服了
You might want to change your shirt.
她们对气味非常敏感
They're very sensitive to smell.
沧龙被认为
The Mosasaurus was thought
是在水面附近捕猎
to have hunted near the surface of the water...
任何被她捕获的动物都会被拖入水下
where it preyed on anything it could sink its teeth into.
包括海龟 大型鱼类 甚至小一些的沧龙
Including turtles, large fish, even smaller Mosasaurus.
好了 各位 让我们看看
Okay, folks, let's see if
今天她在进食后还饿吗
she's still hungry after already eating today.
她有些害羞 所以
She's a little shy, so be
友善些 在她出来后请给些掌声
nice and give her a hand when she comes out.
扎克
Zach!
快看沧龙
The Mosasaurus!
噢 天啊 帅呆了
Oh, my God! That was awesome!
抓紧了 我们将会
Hold on tight. We're gonna
让大家近距离看一下沧龙
give you an even closer look at our Mosasaurus.
她有八十八颗牙齿
It had 88 teeth!
- 还想去看一些更刺激的东西吗 - 想啊
- Wanna see something else cool? - Yeah!
我们几个月前就开始预售门票了
We've been pre-booking tickets for months.
这座公园每年都需要新的噱头
The park needs a new attraction every few years...
这样才能不断吸引公众的兴趣
in order to reinvigorate the public's interest.
就像太空项目
Kind of like the space program.
公司觉得基因改造的产物能够让人眼前一亮
Corporate felt genetic modification would up the wow factor.
她们是恐龙 已经够让人震惊了
They're dinosaurs. Wow enough.
但不是对我们的目标人群而言
Not according to our focus groups.
暴虐霸王龙让我们又一次备受关注
The Indominus Rex makes us relevant again.
暴虐霸王龙
The Indominus Rex?
我们需要一个既吓人又易于发音的名字
We needed something scary and easy to pronounce.
你应该听听一个四岁的孩子说 "古似鸟龙"
You should hear a four-year-old try to say "Archaeornithomimus."
你应该听听你自己怎么发音的
You should hear you try to say it.
这家伙都有哪些基因
So what's this thing made of?
主要的的基因来自霸王龙 其余的是机密
The base genome is a T. Rex. The rest is classified.
你们创造了一种新恐龙 但自己都不知道她是什么吗
You made a new dinosaur but you don't even know what it is?
实验室将成品交给我们
The lab delivers us finished assets,
而我们负责向公众展示
and we show them to the public.
麻烦放下食饵吗
Can we drop a steer, please?
她在这里待多久了
How long has the animal been in here?
从出生到现在
All its life.
从来没见过围墙外的世界吗
Never seen anything outside of these walls?
我们又不能像遛狗一样遛她
We can't exactly walk it.
你们一直喂她吃这个
And you feed it with that?
有问题吗
Is there a problem?
被隔离的动物在成长过程中容易出现各种问题
Animals raised in isolation aren't always the most functional.
你的迅猛龙也是在围场里长大的
Your Raptors are born in captivity.
但是有同伴 她们能相互交流
With siblings. They learn social skills.
而且自她们出生起 我就一直在她们身边
And I imprint on them when they're born.
我们相互信任
There's trust.
而这头恐龙
The only positive
唯一拥有的感情羁绊就是和那台吊车了
relationship this animal has is with that crane.
至少她知道那意味着食物
At least she knows that means food.
这么说 她需要一个朋友
So, she needs a friend.
我们应该给她安排家庭活动日 或者类似的活动吗
We should schedule play-dates? That sort of thing?
可能不是个好主意
Probably not a good idea.
- 她在哪儿 - 在地下室吗
- Where is it? - Is it in the basement?
这里有没有地下一层 没准她在娱乐室玩呢
Is there a downstairs? Maybe it's in the rec room.
她就在这的 我们刚才还来看过
It was just here. We were just here.
(未监测到热能信号)
噢 坏了
Oh, shit.
(未监测到热能信号)
这不对啊
That doesn't make any sense.
这些门最近几周都没有打开过啊
These doors haven't been opened in weeks.
这些抓痕一直都存在吗
Were those claw marks always there?
你觉得她
Do you think it...
噢 天啊
Oh, God.
她的后背有植入物
She has an implant in her back.
我可以从主控室里追踪她
I can track it from the control room.
我们有一头恐龙逃出了围场
We have an asset out of containment.
让武装部队待命 这不是演习
Put ACU on alert. This is not a drill.
虽然我到十三岁时才见到他
Even though I didn't meet him until I was 13...
但是我觉得卡尔比我的亲生父亲还亲
I definitely consider Carl to be more of a dad than my real dad.
- 喂 你好 - 劳瑞
- Yeah, hello? - Lowery.
把暴虐霸王龙的坐标调出来
Get me coordinates on the Indominus.
好的
Okay, yeah.
我现在就调
I'm doing it right now.
这墙有四十英尺高
That wall is 40 feet high.
你不会真觉得她能爬出去吧
Do you really think she could have climbed out?
那得看情况
It depends.
什么情况
On what?
看他们在实验室里到底创造的是什么恐龙
What kind of dinosaur they cooked up in that lab.
等等 什么情况
Wait, what the hell?
她在围场里
It's in the cage.
不 不可能 我刚刚就在那儿啊
No, that's impossible. I was just there.
克莱尔 不会错的 她就在围场里
Claire, I'm telling you, she's in the cage.
等等
Wait a sec.
围场里有人
There are people in there.
快让他们出来
Get them out of there now.
快
Now!
十一号围场 这里是控制中心
Paddock 11, this is Control.
请你们马上撤离围场
You need to evacuate the containment area.
十一号围场
Paddock 11.
十一号围场 你收到了吗
Paddock 11, do you copy?
收到 怎么了
Yeah, what's the problem?
她在围场里 她和你们在一起
It's in the cage! It's in there with you!
快跑
Go!
关上门
Close the door.
我们不能把他和那个怪物关在一起
We can't lock him in there with that thing.
快点关上
Close it now!
你们倒是说句话啊 到底怎么了
Somebody talk to me! What is happening?
妈的
Shit!
所有人保持冷静
Everyone remain calm.
如果她离边界围栏太近
The implant will shock it
植入物就会电击她
if it gets too close to a perimeter fence.
好吧 但她真得移动很快
Okay. It's moving really fast.
这里是控制中心 发出全园警报
This is Control. Put out a park-wide alert.
把电话挂了
Hang up that damn phone, please.
抱歉 刚得到新消息 一切正常
Sorry, I'm getting new information. Everything's fine.
让资产控制部门悄悄的捕获她
Let Asset Containment capture it quietly.
这座公园建成之初就具备了
The very existence of this park is predicated on our ability...
处理这种紧急情况的能力
to handle incidents like this.
这是偶然事件 明白吗
It was an eventuality, okay?
你应该把这点写进观光手册里
You should put that in the brochure.
"最终 总有一头恐龙会把人给吃了"
Eventually, one of these things will eat somebody.
那个围场距最近的景区四英里远
That paddock is 4 miles from the closest attraction.
装甲部队能控制住局面 不会再有人被
ACU can handle this. No one else is gonna get...
吃掉吗
Eaten?
她们能跑多快
How fast can they run?
时速四十公里
40.
饿的时候能达到每小时五十公里
50 when they're hungry.
你之前把她们放出来过吗 见识过她们的能耐吗
You ever open them up, see what they can do?
没有
No.
噢 该死
Oh, shit!
真是吓了我一跳
That got me. It got me.
你觉得怎么样 想带一头回家吗
What do you think? Want to take one home?
嘿 不是开玩笑
Hey, don't joke.
我像你这么大的时候
When I was your age...
救了一只小狼崽
I rescued a wolf pup.
它大概 两个月大吧 几乎还不会走路
It was, like, two months old. It could barely walk.
它以前就睡在我的床边
It used to sleep by my bed.
守护着我
Watch over me.
我的妻子 她拿着一把牛排刀走向我时
My wife, she came at me with a steak knife.
它从她胳膊上咬下了一块肉
It took a chunk out of her arm.
你杀了它吗
Did you put him down?
当然没有
Hell, no.
我们之间有种不可动摇的羁绊 你知道吗
We had an unshakeable bond, you know?
就像你和
Just like you and...
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
德尔塔 她是个女孩
Delta. And she's a girl.
我能不能
Can I...
噢 哇哦
Oh, wow.
十九号警报
Code 19!
- 是那头新恐龙 - 牺牲了两位工作人员
- That's the new one! - They said we lost two guys!
- 十九号警报是什么 - 暴虐霸王龙
- What's a Code 19? - That's Indominus!
资产从围场逃出来了
Asset out of containment.
这些人从不吸取教训
These people, they never learn.
他们现在可得
They're gonna learn all
从这头暴虐龙身上好好学学了
kinds of things about their new asset now.
嘿 是我 我们现在可能有机会了
Yeah, it's me. We might have an opportunity here.
你们以前来过这儿吗
You guys been here before?
如果爸爸妈妈离婚了
If Mom and Dad get divorced,
我们会不会一个跟着妈妈 一个跟着爸爸
will one of us be with Mom and the other with Dad?
什么 你为什么这么说
What? Why would you say that?
因为他们要离婚了
Because they are.
不 他们不会 他们不会离婚的
No, they're not getting... They're not getting divorced.
听我说 你在他们身边待的时间不长
Look, you haven't been around long enough.
他们总是那个样子
They've always been that way.
他们收到了不同律师的信件
They get mail from two different lawyers.
那也说明不了什么
That doesn't mean anything.
我上网查过 他们都是离婚律师
I googled. They're divorce lawyers.
好吧 随便你
All right, whatever.
你知道吗 这不重要
You know what? It doesn't matter.
好吗 我两年之后就要离开家了
Okay? I'm gonna be gone in two years anyway.
我所有朋友的父母都离婚了
All my friends' parents are divorced.
嘿 别这样
Hey, knock it off.
你要哭了吗
You're gonna cry?
听着 所有的东西你都能得到两份
Look, you're gonna get two of everything.
对吗 过两个生日 两个感恩节 两个
Right? Two birthdays, two Thanksgivings. Two...
我不想什么都要两份
I don't want two of everything.
但这不是你能决定的
Yeah, well, it's not up to you.
你总归要长大的
There's a point you have to grow up.
请出示您的证件
I need to see a badge.
先生 先生 请出示您的证件
Sir, sir. I need to see a badge.
外面到底发生了什么
What the hell happened out there?
先生
Sir!
那个围场周围到处都是热感摄像机
There are thermal cameras all over that paddock.
她不可能凭空消失
She did not just disappear!
一定是出现了什么技术故障
It must have been some kind of a technical malfunction.
你没看到吗
Were you not watching?
她在墙上留下爪印分散注意力
She marked up that wall as a distraction.
她想让我们以为她逃跑了
She wanted us to think she escaped!
等等 我们现在谈论的是一只动物
Hold on. We are talking about an animal here.
- 一只高智商动物 - 距离目标四百米
- A highly intelligent animal. - 400 meters to the beacon.
你们居然用非致命武器追捕她
You're going after her with non-lethals.
我们在这只恐龙身上投资了2600万
We have $26 million invested in that asset.
我们不能就这么把她杀了
We can't just kill it.
那些人会死的
Those men are gonna die.
距离目标三百米
300 meters to the beacon.
- 立刻取消这个任务 - 他们能够处理好的
- Call this mission off right now. - They're right on top of it.
- 立刻取消任务 - 这里不是你说了算
- Call it off right now. - You are not in control here!
血液还未凝结
Blood's not clotted yet.
她就在这附近
It's close.
那是什么
What is that?
那是她体内的追踪器 她把它挖出来了
That's her tracking implant. She clawed it out.
她怎么知道这么做
How would it know to do that?
她记得把追踪器植入了哪里
She remembered where they put it in.
她会伪装
It can camouflage!
疏散整座岛屿
Evacuate the island.
那样我们会倒闭的
We'd never reopen.
你们制造出了一头基因混血恐龙 在封闭的空间将她养大
You made a genetic hybrid, raised it in captivity.
她头一次接触外面的一切
She is seeing all of this for the first time.
她甚至不知道自己是什么
She does not even know what she is.
她会杀了所有一切会动的东西
She will kill everything that moves.
你认为她是在刷存在感吗
Do you think the animal is contemplating its own existence?
她在找寻自己处于食物链的哪一环节
She is learning where she fits in the food chain...
我认为你们不会希望她弄明白的
and I'm not sure you want her to figure that out.
资产控制部门
Now, Asset Containment can
能在紧急状况下可以使用实弹
use live ammunition in an emergency situation.
你们的军械库里有M134机枪
You have an M134 in your armory.
把它装到直升机上 然后干掉这个家伙
Put it on a chopper and smoke this thing!
这里有许多家庭
We have families here. I'm not
我不会把这里变成战场的
gonna turn this place into some kind of a war zone.
这里已经是战场了
You already have.
格雷迪先生 如果你不准备帮忙
Mr. Grady, if you're not gonna help,
就没理由继续待在这里了
there's no reason for you to be in here.
我要和实验室里的人谈一谈
I would have a word with your people in the lab.
外面的那个东西 那不是恐龙
That thing out there... that's no dinosaur.
关闭景区北部的所有设施
I'm going to close everything north of the resort.
这是一级戒备 不是演习 请全体出动
This is a Phase One, real world. Bring everyone in.
这是一级戒备 不是演习 重复一遍 这是一级戒备
This is a Phase One, real world. I repeat, this is a Phase One.
把所有游客召回
Bring everyone back in.
软组织被保存了下来
The soft tissue is preserved
因为恐龙血液里含铁
because the iron in the dinosaur's blood...
铁能产生活跃的自由基
generates free radicals, and those are highly reactive.
蛋白质和细胞膜相结合
The proteins and the cell membranes get all mixed up...
起到了天然的保护作用
and act as a natural preservative.
DNA能通过那种方式保存上千年
DNA can survive for millennia that way.
即使琥珀干涸了 他们仍有骨头
Even if the amber mines dry up, they'll still have bones...
闭嘴
Shut up.
你这么盯着她们有什么用
What do you think's gonna happen from you just staring at them?
- 多谢了 伙计 - 不客气
- Thanks, man. - You're welcome.
一路顺风
Enjoy the ride.
孕妇以及患有晕船晕机症的游客
Pregnant women and those who suffer from motion sickness...
在乘坐此观光设施前需咨询医生
should consult with a doctor before riding this ride.
一路顺风
Enjoy the ride.
喂
Hello?
真的吗
Seriously?
抱歉 各位 观光项目停止运行
Sorry, folks. The ride is closed.
请各位乘坐单轨列车撤离
Everyone needs to proceed to the monorail and exit towards the...
拜托 各位 我只是个打工的
Come on, guys, I just work here.
由于技术故障 所有设施现在停止运行
Due to technical difficulties, all our exhibits are now closed.
你知道我不能
You know that I'm not at
随意透露资产的基因成分
liberty to reveal the asset's genetic makeup.
改良后的动物是不可预测的
Modified animals are known to be unpredictable.
她杀了人 亨利
It's killed people, Henry.
那真是不幸
That's unfortunate.
我们为什么要创造一头能伪装自己的恐龙
What purpose could we have for a dinosaur that can camouflage?
她的体内加入了乌贼基因
Cuttlefish genes were added
帮助减缓快速的生长率
to help her withstand an accelerated growth rate.
乌贼体内含有能使
Cuttlefish have chromatophores
皮肤变色的色素体
that allow the skin to change color.
她躲过了热感探测
It hid from thermal technology.
真的吗
Really?
这怎么可能
How is that possible?
树蛙能控制红外线输出
Tree frogs can modulate their infrared output.
我们提取了一些它们的DNA
We used strands from their
帮助她适应热带气候
DNA to adapt her to a tropical climate.
但是我从没想到
But I never imagined...
谁让你这么做的
Who authorized you to do this?
你啊
You did.
"更大"
Bigger.
"更可怕"
Scarier.
"更酷" 我想这是你在备注里用到的字眼吧
Cooler I believe is the word that you used in your memo.
在没有对应的行为特征下
You cannot have an animal with exaggerated predator features...
是不可能出现一个暴力型食肉动物的
without the corresponding behavioral traits.
你现在所做的一切
What you're doing here...
和你已经做过的事
What you have done...
董事会会关了这座公园
The Board will shut down this park,
夺走你的工作和你所建立的一切
seize your work, everything you've built.
哈蒙德这次可保护不了你
And Hammond won't be there to protect you this time.
这一切都是因为我才得以存在
All of this exists because of me.
如果我不创新 自然会有其他人这么做
If I don't innovate, somebody else will.
你要立刻终止这里的所有研究
You are to cease all activities here immediately.
你说得好像我们在做什么疯狂的实验
You are acting like we are engaged in some kind of mad science.
但是我们做的从头到尾都没变过
But we are doing what we have done from the beginning.
侏罗纪世界里的一切都不是天然的
Nothing in Jurassic World is natural.
我们总是在恐龙的基因组里
We have always filled gaps
加入其他动物的DNA
in the genome with the DNA of other animals.
还有 如果她们的基因序列没有被改动
And, if their genetic code was pure,
许多恐龙看上去会很不一样
many of them would look quite different.
但是你并没有要求真实性 你要的是更多牙齿
But you didn't ask for reality. You asked for more teeth.
- 我从未说过要制造出一个怪物 - "怪物" 是一个相对的词语
- I never asked for a monster! - "Monster" Is a relative term.
对于金丝雀来说 猫就是怪物
To a canary, a cat is a monster.
我们只不过是习惯把自己当猫罢了
We're just used to being the cat.
嘿 你们好 我是吉米·肥伦
Hey, there. I'm Jimmy Fallon.
欢迎乘坐陀螺球
Welcome aboard the Gyrosphere,
这是一台由科学创造出来的神奇机器
an amazing machine made possible by science.
我们最关心的是你们的安全
Your safety is our main concern.
因此这个球体是个隐形屏障系统
Which is why you're behind our invisible barrier system...
它能保护你们不受像双脊龙毒液那样的伤害
which protects you from things like Dilophosaurus venom.
一小滴毒液就能让你瘫痪 所以小心点
One drop of this can paralyze you, so watch out.
这是真的毒液吗 是吗
Is this real? It is?
作为额外保护 每个陀螺球外面
And for added protection, each
都有一层氮氧化氯玻璃
vehicle is surrounded by aluminum oxynitride glass.
玻璃十分坚硬 能挡住一颗50口径的子弹
So tough, it can stop a .50-caliber bullet.
陀螺技术能让你保持直立状态
The Gyroscopic technology will keep you upright at all times...
她们在哪儿
Where are they?
所以没什么可担心的
So you've got nothing to worry about.
噢 天呐
Oh, man.
由于技术故障 所有设施现在停止运行
Due to technical difficulties all our exhibits are now closed.
请离开所有观光设施并返回度假区
Please disembark all rides and return to the resort.
别叹气啊 我们还能在外面多待一会儿
Come on, we can stay out a couple more minutes.
可是他们说要关闭设施
But they said it was closed.
克莱尔阿姨给了我们贵宾腕带 不是吗
Aunt Claire gave us special wristbands, right?
我们是贵宾 老弟
We're VIP, dude.
没事 会很有意思的
Come on. It'll be fun.
- 喂 - 扎拉
- Hello? - Zara.
我需要你现在立刻把孩子们带回宾馆
I need you to bring the boys back to the hotel right away.
我不知道 我在到处找他们
I don't know... I've been looking everywhere for them.
慢一点 我听不清你在说什么
Slow down. I can't hear you.
扎克和格雷 他们逃跑了
Zach and Gray, they've run off.
什么
They what?
嘿 克莱尔
Hey, Claire.
扎克 谢天谢地 格雷和你在一起吗
Zach, thank God. Is Gray with you?
我听不清你在说什么 我们在仓鼠球里
I can't really hear you. We're in the hamster ball.
好吧 扎克 听我说
Okay. Zach, listen to me.
我需要你
I need you to...
喂
Hello?
- 喂 - 扎克
- Hello? - Zach?
山谷里还有没归位的陀螺球吗
Are there any Gyrospheres left in the Valley?
没有了 我都清点过了 这是我的工作
No, they're all accounted for. It's my job.
什么
What?
还有一个没有回来
There's one in the field.
派一队突击队员把他们带回来
Send a team of rangers, bring them in.
安保部门 我们正在山谷里进行搜救
Security, we need a search and rescue in the Valley.
要等一会儿 我们现在已经忙不过来了
It's gonna be a while. We've got our hands full out here.
不 不 不 有两名游客失踪了
No, no, no. There are two guests missing!
你们需要优先处理这件事情
You need to make this your top priority!
- 就照她说的做吧 伙计 - 有许多游客都失踪了
- Just do it, man. - There's a lot of guests missing.
我们在尽力搜救
We're doing the best we can.
好吧 我自己去
Okay. Fine. I'll do it myself.
嘿 你觉得我是你现在
Hey, do you think I'm the
需要担心的人吗
one you need to be worried about right now?
走开
Back off!
这里发生了什么
What happened here?
老弟
Dude.
去探险吧
Off-road.
可是他们让我们回去
But they told us to go back.
我只是担心
I'm just worried you're not
你在侏罗纪世界玩得不尽兴
getting the full Jurassic World experience.
克莱尔
Claire!
- 我需要你 - 好的
- I need you. - Okay.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
我的外甥们 他们还在山谷里
My nephews, they're out in the Valley.
拜托你 如果他们有任何闪失
Please, if anything happens to them...
他们多大了
How old?
大一点的那个是高中生 小一点的那个 他
The older one, he's high school age. The younger one, he's...
- 他大概小几岁 - 你不知道你的外甥几岁吗
- He's a few years... - You don't know how old your nephews are?
不 不 这不是个好主意
No, no. Bad idea, bad idea.
- 这是个好主意 - 不 我们会被抓起来的
- Great idea. - No! We're gonna get arrested.
他们会剃光我们的头发 然后
They'll shave our heads, and
我们会在厕所里做根汁饮料的
we're gonna have to make root beer in the toilet.
你胡说什么呢
What are you talking about?
看那儿
There.
看见没 我跟你说过
You see? I told you.
不谢哦 能亲眼近距离地看到
You're welcome. Up close and personal...
四只恐龙
with four dinosauruses.
是甲龙
Ankylosaurus.
我们不应该来这里 而且有五只恐龙
We shouldn't be here. And there's five dinosaurs.
你不是学霸吗 数学没学好吗 看着
Aren't you supposed to be a genius or something? Look.
一 二 三
One, two, three...
四
four.
五
Five.
- 走 走 快走 - 该死
- Go, go, go! - Shit!
抓紧了 兄弟
Hold it together, man!
开啊 快开 快走
Drive! Drive! Go!
我们在这里很安全 对吗
We're safe in here, right?
对 这里绝对安全
Yeah. They're totally safe.
快点
Come on.
接电话 接电话 快接电话
Pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up.
扎克
Zach.
我就要拿到了
I almost got it.
- 扎克 - 怎么了
- Zach? - Yeah?
看
Look.
怎么了
What?
快 快跑
Go! Go!
- 我们得跳下去 - 我不行
- We're gonna have to jump. - I can't.
准备好了吗 一 二 跳
Are you ready? One, two... Come on!
你跳下来了
You jumped.
待在车里
Stay in the car.
嗨
Hi.
我知道 我懂
I know, I know.
没事了
It's all right.
没事的 姑娘
All right, girl.
好了
Okay.
好了 好了
Okay, okay, okay.
没事了 没事了
You're okay. Okay.
她没有吃掉她们
It didn't eat them.
她只是杀了她们用来消遣
It's killing for sport.
各部门待命 准备出发
Units on standby, ready for go.
很好 推迟实况转播
Good. Hold off on that live feed.
现在出现了新情况
We've got an evolving situation here.
他们批准你这么做了吗
Did they give you the green light yet?
他们会的
They will.
欧文 这里有新情况
Owen, we have a situation here.
嘿 你们好 我是吉米·肥伦
Hey, there. I'm Jimmy Fallon.
欢迎乘坐陀螺球
Welcome aboard the Gyrosphere,
这是一台由科学创造出来的神奇机器
an amazing machine made possible by science.
嘿 你们好 我们最关心的是你们的安全
Hey, there. Your safety is our main concern.
现在放轻松 享受观光吧
Now just relax and enjoy the ride.
不 不 不
No, no, no. No.
嘿
Hey.
他们逃出去了
They made it out.
噢 天呐 他们跳下去了
Oh, my God, they jumped.
真勇敢
Brave kids.
扎克 格雷
Zach! Gray!
嘿 我可不是你训练的动物
Hey, I am not one of your damn animals.
听着 那两个孩子还活着
Listen, those kids are still alive...
但是如果你继续这么叫下去的话 我们俩的命可保不住了
but you and I will not be if you continue to scream like that.
那么 你能识别他们的气味
So, you can pick up their scent,
对吗 能追踪他们的脚印吗
can't you? Track their footprints?
我以前是海军 又不是印第安纳瓦霍人
I was with the Navy, not the Navajo.
那我们该怎么办 你说我们该怎么办
So then what should we do? What do you suggest we do?
你回去 我去找他们
You get back. I'll find them.
不 我们一起去找他们
No, we'll find them.
你在丛林里活不过两分钟
You'll last two minutes in there.
况且 你还穿着恨天高
Less, in those ridiculous shoes.
这是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
意思是我准备好了
It means I'm ready to go.
好吧
Okay.
让我把话先说清楚 在外面我说了算
Let's get one thing straight. I'm in charge out here.
你要听我的 完完全全听我的
You do everything I say, exactly as I say it.
- 你说什么 - 放松
- Excuse me? - Just relax.
就像是在丛林里散步一样
It's just like taking a stroll through the woods.
六千五百万年前
65 million years ago.
待这别动
Stay here.
哇
Wow.
你身上还有火柴吗
You still have those matches?
给你
Here you go.
格雷
Gray!
92年的吉普牧马人 沙黄色
1992 Jeep Wrangler Sahara, Sand Beige.
你还记得我们一起修过爷爷那辆旧迈锐宝吗
You remember when we fixed up Grandpa's old Malibu, right?
记得
Yeah.
每当她屠杀完 都会向南行进
Every time this thing kills, it moves further south.
她冲着公园来了
It's headed right for the park.
她为什么要来这儿
Why would she come here?
她能感觉到热辐射
She can sense thermal radiation.
我们的应急措施刚好把所有热量集中在了一处
Our emergency measures just put all the warm bodies in one place.
- 先生 - 生物工程公司
- Sir... - INGEN.
我是霍斯金
Hoskins.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
那你也应该知道我为什么过来
Then you know why I'm here.
我已经从事一项恐龙
I've been working for two
应用项目两年之久
years on an application for those Raptors.
她们能追捕并杀了那头混血恐龙
They can hunt and kill that creature.
但是你的项目是测试她们的智力
But your program was to test their intelligence.
确实如此 而且我们也做到了
Yeah, it was. And we did.
在这过程中 我们还发现了一些别的东西
And in the process, we learned something.
她们能听从命令
They follow orders.
你看 解决你燃眉之急的
You see, the solution to
方法就摆在你面前
your crisis is standing right in front of you.
让我把话说清楚
Let me be as clear as I can.
不能让迅猛龙在这座岛上自由行动
No Velociraptors are going to be set loose on this island.
哦 该死
Oh, shit.
你脑子有问题
You're out of your mind!
你打算怎么处理这些人
What are you going to do with all these people?
这里有两万人 你打算怎么办
You got 20,000 people here. What are you going to do?
他们没有地方可去
They have no place to go.
那头恐龙就是杀人机器
That thing is a killing machine!
而且她不会停止的
And it will not stop.
好吧
Okay.
我有兴趣听听你的计划
I intend to personally look into your project...
但是要遵照公司的道德原则
to determine its viability
来结束她的生命
within the moral principles of this company.
好的 老板
Okay, boss.
你下一步计划是什么
What's your next move?
老板 我联系不上你的驾驶教练
Sir, I can't get a hold of your instructor.
算了 他可能已经撤离了
Never mind. He's likely caught up in the evacuation.
你确定没有别人能开直升飞机了吗
You're sure there's nobody else who can fly a helicopter?
我们不需要别人
We don't need anyone else.
你觉得她就在外面吗
You think it's out there?
我是说 我知道
I mean, I know for a fact
她肯定不在外面 好吗
it is definitely not out there, all right?
我们绝对安全
We're totally safe.
给 拿着这个
Here, go take this.
你比我坚强
You're stronger than me.
好了 启动试试
All right. Turn it over.
成了
It works!
你不是没通过驾照考试吗
I thought you failed your driver's test.
只是科二没过而已
No, only the driving part.
这是他们的东西吗
This one of theirs?
是的
Yeah.
那条路直通公园
That road goes straight back to the park.
他们是怎么把这玩意开走的
How did they even get one of these things started?
(侏罗纪公园)
劳瑞 我们找到她了
Lowery, we found her.
陀螺谷南部
South of the Gyrosphere Valley,
在老公园和鸟舍之间
between the old park and the Aviary.
- 等等 你们在跟踪那头恐龙吗 - 是的
- Wait, are you following the dinosaur? - Yes.
把装甲部队调过来 换上真枪实弹
Get ACU out here. Real guns this time.
装甲部队已经登机了 他们开走了直升飞机
ACU is airborne. They took the helicopter.
是谁开直升飞机
Who's flying it?
你们曾在武装部队服役吗
Did you boys serve in the Armed Forces?
曾驻扎阿富汗 先生
Afghanistan, sir.
你们的上将曾亲临战场和你们一起战斗吗
Did your general ever fly into battle with you?
放心 我控制住了
Got it! Got it.
我们发现目标了 陀螺谷南部
We have eyes on the target, south of the Aviary.
请前往交火
Proceed and engage.
打起精神来 兄弟们
Come on! Look alive, boys!
打起精神来
Look alive!
10点钟方向 鸟舍旁边
10 o'clock! By the birdcage!
不 不 不 不
No, no, no! No, no, no.
看来狐狸进了鸡笼了
Looks like the fox got in the henhouse.
拉高 拉高 快 快
Pull up! Pull up! Up, up, up!
鸟舍出现了一个缺口
We have a breach in the Aviary.
快进树林 快 快
Trees, the trees! Go! Go!
(危险 万伏高压)
这下好了
Okay, that's it.
我们安全了
We're safe now.
快 快 快
Go, go, go! Go, go, go!
快
Hurry up!
嘿
Hey!
- 救命 - 快开门 让我们进去
- Help! - Open the gate! Let us in!
- 快开门 - 快点
- Open it up! - Come on!
第一次遇见这种情况
That's a first.
快开门
Open the gate!
- 快开门 - 让我们进去
- Open the gate! - Let us in!
鸟舍工作人员请注意 围场出现缺口
Attention Aviary employees, there has been a containment breach.
喂
Hello?
克莱尔 我们在监控上看到你的外甥了
Claire, we spotted the boys on surveillance.
他们刚从西门进来
They're approaching the west gate.
我现在就过去
I'm headed there now.
好的 好的 待在那里
Okay, okay. Stay right there.
我这就过去 守着他们 哪儿也别去
I'm on my way. Stay right with them.
嘿
Hey!
快上来
Get on!
女士们先生们 由于围场故障
Ladies and gentlemen, due to a containment anomaly...
请所有游客马上进入室内
all guests must take shelter immediately.
女士们先生们 由于围场故障
Ladies and gentlemen, due to a containment anomaly...
请所有游客马上进入室内
all guests must take shelter immediately.
女士们先生们 由于围场故障
Ladies and gentlemen, due to a containment anomaly...
请所有游客马上进入室内
all guests must take shelter immediately.
所有单位注意 请在木板路就位
All units, take position on boardwalk.
使用液体镇定剂 请勿使用弹药
Use liquid tranquilizers. Do not fire live ammunition.
克莱尔 快
Claire, come on!
别跑了
Stop running!
别傻站在那儿
Don't just stand there!
快 快进屋
Go! Get inside now!
扎克
Zach!
格雷
Gray!
- 克莱尔阿姨 - 快 快
- Aunt Claire! - Go, go!
克莱尔
Claire!
不 注意
No! Hold your...
那是克莱尔阿姨吗
Is that Aunt Claire?
是他们 扎克
It's them! Zach!
格雷
Gray!
哦 天啊 谢天谢地 怎么回事 这是怎么了
Oh, my God! Thank God! What happened? What is this?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你们跑哪儿去了 为什么不回来
Where did you go? Why didn't you come back?
- 我快担心死你们了 - 那是谁
- I was so worried about you. - Who's that?
我的同事
We work together.
嘿
Hey.
- 我们得走了 - 好的 快来 快
- We gotta go. - Okay. Come on. Come on, come on.
嘿 嘿 你们不能就这么大摇大摆走进来
Hey, hey! You guys can't just be walking up in...
西蒙·马斯拉尼的死是场悲剧
Simon Masrani's death was a tragedy.
新的任务是防止更多人员伤亡
The new mission is to prevent further loss of life.
他们是谁
Who are these guys?
就等你问呢
I'm glad you asked.
你们全部被解除职务了
You're all relieved of duty.
现在由新的团队接手
There's a new team on the ground.
劳瑞 我正在往你那里去
Lowery, I'm on my way back to you.
别回来
That's a bad idea.
董事会刚刚给生物工程公司的
The board assigned emergency
安保部门指派了新的应急行动
ops to INGEN's private security division.
一个叫什么霍斯金的人负责
This guy Hoskins is in charge.
他有一个疯狂的计划
And he has this insane
利用迅猛龙来围捕暴虐霸王龙
plan to use the Raptors to hunt the Indominus.
你说 "利用迅猛龙" 是什么意思
What do you mean "Use the Raptors"?
这狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
你不该爆粗口的
You shouldn't say "Bitch."
把孩子们带到安全的地方
Take the kids. Get them someplace safe.
- 好了 该死 快开车 - 开快点
- You got this! Damn it, drive! - Go faster!
这里一点也不安全
This does not feel safe.
我们能和你待在一起吗
Can we stay with you?
我不会再离开你们半步了
I am never leaving you as long as you live.
不不 我们说的是他
No, no, no. Him.
是啊 当然是他了
Yeah, definitely him.
嘿 看这里
Hey! Right here.
看着我
Right here.
她想看哪里就看哪里
She looks at what she wants.
她一般看到的都是食物
Usually what she wants to eat.
母鸡终于到了
The mother hen has finally arrived.
给我滚出这里 离我的恐龙远一点
Get the hell out of here and stay away from my animals.
霍斯金 你盼着这种事发生 你这个狗娘养的
Hoskins, you wanted this to happen, you son of a bitch!
哦 天啊
Oh, Jesus!
在你能想通这个任务之前
How many more people have to die
你还想眼睁睁地看着多少人去送死
before this mission starts to make sense to you?
这不是任务
It's not a mission.
是实地测验
It's a field test.
现在已经上升到生物工程的层面了
This is an INGEN situation now.
听着 明天一早
Okay, there are gonna be
就会有大型轮船抵达这里
cruise ships that show up here at first light.
所有人都将安全撤离
Everybody's gonna get off this island.
你明天看到的新闻
You're gonna watch a news
将会是你们拯救了多少条生命
story tomorrow about how you all saved lives.
不不 更好的是
No, no, no, better yet...
你的恐龙拯救了多少条生命
how your animals saved lives.
她们从来没出去过 这太扯了
They've never been out of containment. It's crazy.
开始行动吧
Let's move it out!
已经这样决定了
This is happening!
有没有你都一样
With or without you.
我们知道她现在在第五区
We know that she is in sector five.
这场游戏我们称之为躲猫猫 是气味演习
This is a game we call hide-and-seek. It's a scent drill.
我们已经和这些恐龙练习了上千遍
We've done it about a thousand times with these animals.
当她们锁定目标 她们一定会锁定
When they get on target, and they will get on target...
等待发动进攻
wait to engage.
迅猛龙是群聚猎人
Velociraptors are pack hunters.
她们会把猎物集中在攻击范围内
They like to herd the animal into a kill zone.
那时就是我们发动进攻的时候
That's when we take our shot.
一枪命中
Get a clear shot, wait on
听我命令 尽全力攻击
my command and give her everything you got.
我们只有一个目标 先生们
We got one good target, gentlemen.
不要伤了我的迅猛龙
Do not shoot my Raptors.
拜托了
Please.
放松 布鲁
Easy, Blue.
放轻松
Easy.
乖女孩
Attagirl.
你吓不到我的
You don't scare me.
欧文
Owen.
她们安全吗
Are they safe?
当然不安全了
No, they're not.
她们叫什么名字
What are their names?
那边那头是查理
Well, you got Charlie.
那是艾蔻 这是德尔塔
There's Echo. Here is Delta.
这头叫布鲁 她是老二
This one's called Blue. She's the beta.
那谁是老大
Who's the alpha?
站在你面前的就是 小子
You're looking at him, kid.
看见了吧
See?
绝对安全
Totally safe.
好了 进去吧 快
All right, get in. Come on.
上去坐好
Get in there.
如果你们需要我 我就在前面驾驶座
If you need me, I'll be right up front.
打开那扇窗户就行
Just open that window.
好吗
Okay?
系好安全带
Put your seatbelts on.
好吧 那你们就
Okay, so just...
拉着手好了
hold hands.
什么东西都进不来的 对吧
Nothing's getting in here, right?
嘿
Hey.
你还记得老房子里的鬼吗
Do you remember that ghost at the old house?
就是车库里的那个
Remember the one in the garage?
我保护了你 不是吗
I protected you, right?
你用一把尺子和一个纸盘子做了一把战斧
You made a battle axe out of a ruler and a paper plate.
是啊 看 只要我在你身边 没有什么能伤害你的 明白吗
Yeah. See, nothing is gonna get you while I'm around, okay?
但你又不能永远在我身边
But you're not always gonna be around.
这个嘛
Yeah, well...
嘿
Hey.
我们是兄弟 好吗
We're brothers, okay?
我们永远都是兄弟
We'll always be brothers
永远都会回到对方身边的
and we'll always come back to one another.
无论发生什么
No matter what.
无论发生什么吗
No matter what?
是的
No matter what.
太棒了
Awesome.
出发吧
Here we go.
你男朋友真屌
Your boyfriend's a badass.
想象一下如果我们在托拉博拉（阿富汗）养这种宠物
Imagine if we had these puppies in Tora Bora.
你有录下来吗
Are you recording this thing?
她们减速了
They're slowing down.
她们有发现了
They got something.
这样不行 不行 不行 少儿不宜
You know what? No, no, no. You guys are not gonna watch this.
把窗户关好了
Keep the window closed.
情况不对
Something's wrong.
她们在交流
They're communicating.
我知道他们为什么不告诉我们 它另一部分基因是什么了
I know why they wouldn't tell us what it's made of.
为什么
Why?
它也有迅猛龙的基因
That thing's part Raptor.
他们在磨蹭什么 开火
What's taking them so long? Light it up!
开火
Engage!
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
注意正后方
Watch your six.
迅猛龙们有新老大了
Raptors got a new alpha.
快回到车里 快
To the vehicles now!
撤退
Fall back!
不
No!
布鲁
Blue!
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
所有人都死了吗
Is everybody dead?
不 不 不 大家都很好
No, no, no. Everyone is fine.
别对他说谎
Don't lie to him.
他很害怕 当人们害怕的时候 撒点谎也无伤大雅
He's scared. It's okay to lie when people are scared.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
宝贝 你会安全到家的 好吗 我保证
Sweetheart, you will, okay? I promise.
明天你就能回家了
Tomorrow you will be home...
而你妈妈永远也不会让我再见到你们了
and your mother will never let me see you again.
快离开这里 快走
Get out of here! Go!
她们来了
They're coming!
在后面坐好了
Just hold on back there.
- 快启动啊 - 我不知道怎么启动
- Turn it on. - I don't know how.
你们哥俩还好吗
Are you boys okay?
嘿 刚才那一幕你看到了吗
Hey, did you see that?
我等不及要告诉妈妈了
I can't wait to tell Mom.
拜托 不要 千万不要告诉你妈妈这事儿 永远不要
Please, no. Do not tell your mother about that, ever.
- 欧文 - 欧文
- Owen! - Owen!
我们必须要躲进室内 跟我来
We gotta get indoors. Follow me.
劳瑞 我们往你那边去了 找架直升机来
Lowery, we're headed your way. Call in a chopper.
所有东西都要清点好
Everything must be accounted for.
启动所有备用发电机
I want all backup generators online.
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?
计划有变 任务进行得不顺利
Change of plans. Mission took a jog to the left.
我要带部队撤离了
I'm taking everything off-site.
胚胎在这里很安全
The embryos are safe here.
依靠发电机它们能存活八周
They can live up to eight weeks on the generators.
不 不 你听好了 公园明天一早就会宣告破产了
No, no. You listen. The park's gonna be Chapter 11 by morning.
好吧 我们的小计划要拿到部队里去尝试一下
Okay, our little side project's about to get a shot in the arm.
我可不想让一群律师插手
I don't want a bunch of lawyers messing around
这些他们根本不懂的东西
with something that they don't understand.
明白了吗
You get it?
嘿 不说话我就当你是默认了
Hey! I'm gonna take that as a yes.
女士们先生们 感谢你们的耐心等待
Ladies and gentlemen, we'd like to thank you for your patience.
下一班轮渡将在45分钟后离开
The next ferry will be leaving in 45 minutes.
如果您需要紧急医疗救护
If you require immediate medical attention, please
请到最近的健康服务站寻求帮助
report to the nearest health service station.
你就是这么想的吗
Is this what you had in mind?
好了 各位 我们的撤离点在东码头
Okay, people. We have an extraction point at the east dock.
嘿
Hey.
他们说我们得撤离了 有艘船在等着
They said we had to evacuate. There's a boat.
你来吗
You coming?
得有人坚守阵地
Someone has to stay behind.
不 我有男朋友了
No. I have a boyfriend.
我不知道你们真的 在一起了
I didn't know that you guys were, like, together-together.
我们是在一起了
We are.
那很好啊 可从来没听你提起过他
That's good. You don't mention him, ever.
我一向公私分明
No, I'm at work.
不 好吧
No, no, no. Yeah.
- 好吧 - 好的
- Well... - Yeah, okay.
- 很好 - 很好
- Great. - Great.
- 好吧 - 好吧
- Okay. - Okay.
- 你会没事的 对吧 - 是的
- Are you gonna be okay? - Yeah.
好吧 拜
Okay, bye.
霍斯金在哪儿
Where's Hoskins?
他要我们把你和这些资产送到安全的地方
He's sending you and the assets to a secure location.
但我们的协议还是有效的对吧
But our deal is still intact?
不用担心 我们会好好照顾你的 出发了
Don't worry. You'll be well taken care of. Let's go!
感谢各位光临侏罗纪世界
Thank you for visiting Jurassic World.
希望您玩得愉快
We hope you enjoyed your adventure.
不要忘了去礼品店哦 请记住
Don't forget to visit the gift shop, and remember...
玛格丽塔酒吧有饮品减价活动哦
It's always happy hour at Margaritaville.
快过来 快 进去
Come on, come on. Go inside.
去主控室 那边
Control room. That way.
(哈蒙德创意实验室)
他们疏散了实验室
They evacuated the lab.
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
你还不够级别过问这事 宝贝
I'm afraid that's above your pay grade, honey.
亨利在哪儿
Where's Henry?
吴博士是我们的人
Dr. Wu works for us.
那不是真正的恐龙
That's not a real dinosaur.
当然不是了 小子
No, it ain't, kid.
但总要有人确保这家公司有光明的钱途
But somebody's gotta make sure that this company has a future.
试想一下
Imagine...
这只恐龙 有体型
that one, a fraction of the size...
又致命
deadly...
还聪明
intelligent...
能躲过最先进的军队科技
able to hide from the most advanced military technology.
一个不同于我们所见过的活武器
A living weapon unlike anything we've ever seen.
你们不懂吗 数万年的进化 我们又从中学到了什么
You see? Millions of years of evolution... what did we learn?
大自然就是上天赐予的礼物
Nature is the gift that just...
哦 靠
Oh, shit!
别激动
Easy.
Easy, boy.
别激动 嘿 嘿
Easy. Hey, hey.
我们是同一战线的 不是吗 对吗
We're on the same side, right? Right?
放松
Easy.
我跟你是一伙的
I'm on your side.
不 孩子们 这边 快
No, boys. This way. Come on.
快点 快
Come on. Come on.
你们就是这样捕猎的 对吗
That's how it is, huh?
放松
Easy.
就是这样
That's it.
24颗 50颗
24, 50.
我们需要更多
We need more.
更多什么
More what?
牙齿 我们需要更多牙齿
Teeth. We need more teeth.
好吧 你们在这儿等着
Okay, so, you just wait here.
会没事的
It's gonna be fine.
劳瑞 你还在吗
Lowery, are you still there?
嘿 你在哪儿
Hey, where are you?
把9号围场的门打开
I need you to open Paddock 9.
9号围场
Paddock 9?
你开玩笑吧
You kidding?
该死 劳瑞 一辈子哪怕像个男人一次 好吗
Damn it, Lowery, be a man and do something for once in your life.
你为什么非要对我人身攻击啊
Why did you have to make it personal?
快跑
Run!
快跑 快 快
Go! Go, go!
哦 天啊 你们父母来了 他们来了
Oh, my God, it's your parents. It's your parents.
快来 快啊
Come on, come on.
你们还好吗 哦 我的宝贝
Are you okay? Oh, baby.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
快过来
Come here.
宝贝
Sweetie.
那我们接下来做什么
So, what do we do now?
最好待在一起
Probably stick together.
为了生存
For survival.